<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SixPraxis</title>
    <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SixPraxis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sixpraxis.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Love</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/love/</guid>
      <description>Love Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up We&amp;rsquo;ve got a decent amount of open ports, including web, msrpc, and SMB. Taking a look at port 80 show a login form for a voting system, 443 gives a 403 forbidden, 5000 is a 403, 5985 404, 5986 404, and 47001 is a 404. SMB doesn&amp;rsquo;t allow anonymous login. After digging around for a while and fuzzing for directories, a line from an nmap script scan caught my eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - TheNotebook</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/thenotebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/thenotebook/</guid>
      <description>TheNotebook Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up Two open ports, 22 and 80, one filtered port 10010. Pulling up the website takes us to a notebook page with a register and login link. Let&amp;rsquo;s look around.
The register page lets you sign up without verification. I made a user test1 : password1. The log in page provides error messages that let you verify if a user exists, &amp;ldquo;admin&amp;rdquo; exists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Armageddon</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/armageddon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/armageddon/</guid>
      <description>Armageddon Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up Initial scan shows two ports, 22 and 80. Checking out the web port shows us a welcome page with a login. WFuzz finds a few directories we can check out. Looking through the files in the /includes directory points towards this being a drupal 7.56 install. Searchsploit shows multiple RCE exploits called drupalgeddon. Drupalgeddon2&amp;rsquo;s version range matches our version, let&amp;rsquo;s give it a shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Ophiuchi</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/ophiuchi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/ophiuchi/</guid>
      <description>Ophiuchi Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up Two ports are open, 22 and 8080. Pulling up 8080 brings up an online yaml parser page. Submitting text brings up a page with Due to security reason this feature has been temporarily on hold. We will soon fix the issue!. Putting a &#39; in the input and hitting submit pulls up an error page, revealing that the page is using snakeyaml.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Spectra</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/spectra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/spectra/</guid>
      <description>Spectra Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up Initial scan shows three open ports, 22, 80, and 3306. The web port takes us to a temporary looking page that offers a link to a wordpress site and says to use that until they get Jira set up. Another link on the page takes us to an error message saying that a database connection could not be established.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Tenet</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/tenet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/tenet/</guid>
      <description>Tenet Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up Two ports, 22 and 80. Pulling up 80 by IP shows the Apache2 Ubuntu Default Page, but pulling it up by tenet.htb after adding it to my hosts file pulls up a WordPress site. User &amp;ldquo;protagonist&amp;rdquo; has authored all of the posts, one comment by user &amp;ldquo;neil&amp;rdquo; who seems to be a part of the organization.
Possible lead in neil&amp;rsquo;s comment did you remove the sator php file and the backup?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - ScriptKiddie</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/scriptkiddie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/scriptkiddie/</guid>
      <description>ScriptKiddie Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up Initial scan showed two open ports, 22 and 5000. 5000 hosts a web server, so we&amp;rsquo;ll start there. We&amp;rsquo;re greeted with a page titled &amp;ldquo;k1d&#39;5 h4ck3r t00l5&amp;rdquo;, which looks like it&amp;rsquo;ll run certain shell commands with user supplied input. Among the commands are nmap, msfvenom, and searchsploit. Tacking on commands with &amp;amp; doesn&amp;rsquo;t work, neither does using single or double quotes to escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Delivery</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/delivery/</guid>
      <description>Delivery Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up First scans show two open ports, 22 and 80. Opening up the address in a web browser brings us to a welcome page with a link to a helpdesk subdomain(http://helpdesk.delivery.htb/) and a &amp;ldquo;Contact Us&amp;rdquo; button. To access this subdomain, I added it to my hosts file with the box&amp;rsquo;s ip.
The subdomain takes us to a support ticketing portal powered by OSTicket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Ready</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/ready/</guid>
      <description>Ready Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up Two open ports, 22 and a web server on 5080. The web server is hosting an instance of GitLab. Signing up works without verification and lets me onto the GitLab dashboard. There&amp;rsquo;s one public project called ready-channel, created by user &amp;ldquo;dude&amp;rdquo;. The project repo houses a drupal install and we pick up some mysql credentials(drupaluser : %%cHzhNC=k9yYN!T) from the settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Apocalypse 2021</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/cyberapocalypse2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/cyberapocalypse2021/</guid>
      <description>Cyber Apocalypse 2021 I came into this one pretty out of practice. I haven&amp;rsquo;t spent much time on the pentesting front since I started studying for my CCNA a few months back. I still had a lot of fun with it and will definitely be participating next year.
Categories  Web Crypto Reversing Forensics Misc  Web Inspector Gadget Opening the url in a browser gives us a page showing a robot flying through space with CHTB{ in text above it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Admirer</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/admirer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/admirer/</guid>
      <description>Admirer 10.10.10.187 Write-Up Recon with NMAP shows three ports. 21, 22, 80. No progress on the first two. The apache service on 80 displays a gallery website with no useful links. Robots.txt reveals /admin-dir, but we do not have permission to view it. Fuzzing /admin-dir/ revealed contacts.txt, which contains some admin and developer e-mails, and credentials.txt, which has creds for an FTP, Wordpress, and internal mail account. Connecting to the FTP server gives us an SQL dump and backup of the site files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Blunder</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/blunder/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/blunder/</guid>
      <description>Blunder 10.10.10.191 by SixPraxis
Write-Up Initial recon shows one open port running an HTML service. Inspection reveals a blog running on Bludit CMS v3.9.2. Known exploits for this platform include an authentication brute force mitigation bypass and an authenticated code execution. Fuzzing found a todo.txt, which has the name fergus in it. After creating a brute force script and making no progress, we notice that in the Stephen King blog post there is a name that is oddly unspaced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Buff</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/buff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/buff/</guid>
      <description>Buff 10.10.10.198 by SixPraxis Write-Up Nmap scans showed 2 open ports, 7680 running an unidentified service and 8080 running a gym website. The about page on the website displayed &amp;ldquo;Made using Gym Management Software 1.0&amp;rdquo;. An RCE vulnerability is present in the software and an exploit is publicly available. A pre-made exploit was downloaded from exploit db, number 48506. After fixing the code in the exploit, it was used to upload a web shell interface to the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Omni</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/omni/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/omni/</guid>
      <description>Omni 10.10.10.204 by SixPraxis Write-Up Pulling up port 8080 in a web browser asks for a login for &amp;ldquo;Windows Device Portal&amp;rdquo;. After looking at the ports and doing some research it&amp;rsquo;s very likely that the machine is running Windows IoT core. An exploit called SirepRAT exists for this that lets an attacker remotely execute commands. After cloning the script from git hub, python2 SirepRAT.py 10.10.10.204 GetFileInformationFromDevice --remote_path &amp;quot;C:\Windows\System32\WindowsPowerShell\v1.0\powershell.exe&amp;quot; was issued to confirm the existence of the powershell executable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - OpenKeyS</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/openkeys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/openkeys/</guid>
      <description>OpenKeyS 10.10.10.199 by SixPraxis Write-Up Two open ports were available at the time of scanning. One ssh port, one http port. The http port displayed a simple login page. Fuzzing found the /includes/ which contained auth.php and auth.php.swp. VIM swap files contain changes that have been made to a file, but not yet saved. Downloading auth.php.swp and using strings to open the file revealed a potential username &amp;ldquo;jennifer&amp;rdquo; and another file at .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Passage</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/passage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/passage/</guid>
      <description>Passage 10.129.5.60 (Release Arena) by SixPraxis Write-Up Port 80 contained a news blog being run on the CuteNews cms software. http://10.129.5.60/CuteNews/ provided the version number of 2.1.2 and a login page. Searching the version number revealed three known exploits:
CuteNews 2.1.2 - &#39;avatar&#39; Remote Code Execution (Metasploit) | php/remote/46698.rb CuteNews 2.1.2 - Arbitrary File Deletion | php/webapps/48447.txt CuteNews 2.1.2 - Authenticated Arbitrary File Upload | php/webapps/48458.txt Exploit 48458 allows file upload with a low level user, so the attacker registered for the website with gunship : gunship1 to get access to vulnerable area of the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - SneakyMailer</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/sneakymailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/sneakymailer/</guid>
      <description>SneakyMailer 10.10.10.197 by SixPraxis Write-Up Initial scans showed FTP, SMTP, POP3, and HTTP ports. Port 80 displayed a dashboard with team member names and emails. The attacker used cewl to scrape the emails,  cewl -w cewlwords.txt -e --email_file emails.txt http://sneakycorp.htb and then awk -F @ &#39;{print $1}&#39; emails.txt &amp;gt; emailstrimmed.txt to create a list of usernames without the @sneakycorp.htb extension. Using the email list with the python version of smtp-user-enum found all of the accounts valid on this mail server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Tabby</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/tabby/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/tabby/</guid>
      <description>Tabby 10.10.10.194 by SixPraxis Write-Up Initial nmap scans revealed three ports, two of which were running HTTP services, the other being SSH. A server rental website resided on port 80 and Apache Tomcat 9 on port 8080. Investigating the site on port 80 revealed that news.php contained an LFI vulnerability. Tests successfully accessed /etc/passwd by requesting http://target.htb/news.php?file=../../../../../../../../etc/passwd. No further vulnerabilities were found on port 80.
Port 8080 displayed the default page for Tomcat, listing internal paths to configuration files and links to the manager web interfaces used to manage the installation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Worker</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/worker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/worker/</guid>
      <description>Worker 10.10.10.203 by SixPraxis Write-Up Nmap scans showed three open ports. The two web ports revealed no useful information, one had a default IIS and the other a 404 page. Fuzzing found no additional pages. To investigate port 3690, the attacker used netcat, getting a response showing available SVN commands.
$nc 10.10.10.203 3690 ( success ( 2 2 ( ) ( edit-pipeline svndiff1 accepts-svndiff2 absent-entries commit-revprops depth log-revprops atomic-revprops partial-replay inherited-props ephemeral-txnprops file-revs-reverse list ) ) ) svn list svn://10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
