<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>medium on SixPraxis</title>
    <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/tags/medium/</link>
    <description>Recent content in medium on SixPraxis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sixpraxis.github.io/tags/medium/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HTB - TheNotebook</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/thenotebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/thenotebook/</guid>
      <description>TheNotebook Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up Two open ports, 22 and 80, one filtered port 10010. Pulling up the website takes us to a notebook page with a register and login link. Let&amp;rsquo;s look around.
The register page lets you sign up without verification. I made a user test1 : password1. The log in page provides error messages that let you verify if a user exists, &amp;ldquo;admin&amp;rdquo; exists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Ophiuchi</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/ophiuchi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/ophiuchi/</guid>
      <description>Ophiuchi Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up Two ports are open, 22 and 8080. Pulling up 8080 brings up an online yaml parser page. Submitting text brings up a page with Due to security reason this feature has been temporarily on hold. We will soon fix the issue!. Putting a &#39; in the input and hitting submit pulls up an error page, revealing that the page is using snakeyaml.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Tenet</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/tenet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/tenet/</guid>
      <description>Tenet Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up Two ports, 22 and 80. Pulling up 80 by IP shows the Apache2 Ubuntu Default Page, but pulling it up by tenet.htb after adding it to my hosts file pulls up a WordPress site. User &amp;ldquo;protagonist&amp;rdquo; has authored all of the posts, one comment by user &amp;ldquo;neil&amp;rdquo; who seems to be a part of the organization.
Possible lead in neil&amp;rsquo;s comment did you remove the sator php file and the backup?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Ready</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/ready/</guid>
      <description>Ready Contents  Write Up Recon Credentials Notes  Write Up Two open ports, 22 and a web server on 5080. The web server is hosting an instance of GitLab. Signing up works without verification and lets me onto the GitLab dashboard. There&amp;rsquo;s one public project called ready-channel, created by user &amp;ldquo;dude&amp;rdquo;. The project repo houses a drupal install and we pick up some mysql credentials(drupaluser : %%cHzhNC=k9yYN!T) from the settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - OpenKeyS</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/openkeys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/openkeys/</guid>
      <description>OpenKeyS 10.10.10.199 by SixPraxis Write-Up Two open ports were available at the time of scanning. One ssh port, one http port. The http port displayed a simple login page. Fuzzing found the /includes/ which contained auth.php and auth.php.swp. VIM swap files contain changes that have been made to a file, but not yet saved. Downloading auth.php.swp and using strings to open the file revealed a potential username &amp;ldquo;jennifer&amp;rdquo; and another file at .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Passage</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/passage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/passage/</guid>
      <description>Passage 10.129.5.60 (Release Arena) by SixPraxis Write-Up Port 80 contained a news blog being run on the CuteNews cms software. http://10.129.5.60/CuteNews/ provided the version number of 2.1.2 and a login page. Searching the version number revealed three known exploits:
CuteNews 2.1.2 - &#39;avatar&#39; Remote Code Execution (Metasploit) | php/remote/46698.rb CuteNews 2.1.2 - Arbitrary File Deletion | php/webapps/48447.txt CuteNews 2.1.2 - Authenticated Arbitrary File Upload | php/webapps/48458.txt Exploit 48458 allows file upload with a low level user, so the attacker registered for the website with gunship : gunship1 to get access to vulnerable area of the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - SneakyMailer</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/sneakymailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/sneakymailer/</guid>
      <description>SneakyMailer 10.10.10.197 by SixPraxis Write-Up Initial scans showed FTP, SMTP, POP3, and HTTP ports. Port 80 displayed a dashboard with team member names and emails. The attacker used cewl to scrape the emails,  cewl -w cewlwords.txt -e --email_file emails.txt http://sneakycorp.htb and then awk -F @ &#39;{print $1}&#39; emails.txt &amp;gt; emailstrimmed.txt to create a list of usernames without the @sneakycorp.htb extension. Using the email list with the python version of smtp-user-enum found all of the accounts valid on this mail server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Worker</title>
      <link>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/worker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sixpraxis.github.io/posts/worker/</guid>
      <description>Worker 10.10.10.203 by SixPraxis Write-Up Nmap scans showed three open ports. The two web ports revealed no useful information, one had a default IIS and the other a 404 page. Fuzzing found no additional pages. To investigate port 3690, the attacker used netcat, getting a response showing available SVN commands.
$nc 10.10.10.203 3690 ( success ( 2 2 ( ) ( edit-pipeline svndiff1 accepts-svndiff2 absent-entries commit-revprops depth log-revprops atomic-revprops partial-replay inherited-props ephemeral-txnprops file-revs-reverse list ) ) ) svn list svn://10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
